Jeremy Li

39 Florence St, Boston, MA, 02148 Tel: (781)-605-7163

Website: *jeremyli.space* Email: jeremyli.9023@gmail.com

Objective

A software engineer also can get passionate about product. 3+ years Startup engineering experiences not only bolster my technical capability but nurture product visions and business acumen. I desire to launch a captivated meaningful product one day with bunch of talents to deliver delightful experience for others.

Work Experiences

Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA

Software Engineer, Developer Integration

Mar, 2018 – Now

- Built friction-less third-party plugins/toolings to support user-friendly security customer community.
- Scaled Jira standalone server over AWS cloud-based ecosystem to reduce massive single point failures.
- Built up customer metrics via SumoLogic to track real-time API calling through the entire integration eco-system(7 product lines),help Sr. management and partnership make strategic roadmap decisions.
- Exposed proactively in Agile Scrum and DevOps realm(A/B testing, canary releases) and gained better product sense and SaaS enterprise product insights.

CA Technologies, Burlington, MA

Software Engineer I, Developer Integration

Nov, 2017 - Mar, 2018

• Implement and maintain a range of plugins/extensions of SaaS application security scan platform, led to increased at least 20% efficiency of proceeding application security scanning assessment.

Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA (Acquired by CA Technologies March, 2017)

Software Engineer I, Core Platform

Jun, 2016 - Nov,2017

- Collaborated with multi-functional teams across different department such as Design, PM and Customer Support to bring new features/enhancements onto quarterly release circle by using Agile.
- Tackled customer-faced technical problems, refactored the deprecated codebase and integrated with CI/CD pipeline, improved our SDLC for a more reliable TDD environment.
- Been UX council member dedicated to my team, to unify and adopt best practice of front-end effort needed along with product roadmap.

Philips of North America, New York

Software Research Intern, Acute Care Solution

Sep - Dec, 2014

- Processed and transformed healthcare dataset that can be later used for EMR research purposes.
- Implemented a periodic recommendation for patient monitoring system by using Python.

Technical Skills

- ► Languages: Java, Javascript/ES6, Python, R, HTML5/CSS3(Sass/LESS)
 ► Databases: MySQL
- ▶ Web Framework: React, D3.js, Jest, Bootstrap, Foundation, Gulp, Bower, RESTful, Spring Boot.
- ▶ DevOps: AWS, Jenkins, Docker ▶ Other: Git/Bitbucket, Jira/Confluence, Agile, Axure, Balsamiq.
- ► Certification: PSM I (Professional Scrum Master), Google Analytics IQ.

Education

Northeastern University, College of Engineering, Boston, MA

M.S. in Information Systems

Sep, 2015

Related Course: Application Engineering, Web Development, Advanced Data Science, Organization Mgt.

Central South University, College of Engineering, Changsha, China Monash University, College of Engineering, Melbourne, Australia

B.S. in Computational Material Engineering

Jun, 2013

Honors: 2nd prize in Challenge Cup Innovative Technology; "Most Influential Member", Engineer-Club. Leadership: College Vice-President of Innovation and Entrepreneurship Association.

Academic Projects

U.S. Airlines On-Time Performance Analytics Project

- Cleaned, assembled and transformed the large-scale datasets from RITA.(K-Mean, Hclust, dbscan).
- Delivered graphs and charts for visualizing air flight on-time performance analysis outcomes.

Healthcare Medical-Malpractice Informatics System

- Designed a national-wide model independently for adverse reporting of the healthcare system by Java.
- Implemented a hierarchical access system to safeguard patient privacy under aggressive deadlines.